Seen it, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp, gulp!
What are you going to dance today, in 15cm heels?
Countdown!
Countdown! I want to dance!
15cm heels now.
I guess, through the video, we're all the same height.
I often put Chessie in there.
So now I'm 175cm, 185cm, and 171cm.
The world is. The world is tall, isn't it?
But is it a challenge to see if you can dance like this?
I don't usually dance this high even at live performances.
This might be my first time.
Moreover, I have never danced in pinwheels.
But when I have heel lessons sometimes, they are 8cm high.
Double?
A little less than double.
I'm going to dance the countdown in heels that are about twice as high.
Do you want to go?
Let's go. Let's start the video!
This time, I'm wearing D-Holic's costume.
Let the music begin!
My eyes are waking up.
But I can dance.
Are you okay?
I'm scared, I'm scared!
Oh, no!
and then you're being killed by lia.
Plus the season.
Mmm.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm going to be sooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooI'm going to be suited.
I've got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, this place is bad.
Wow.
But you know what?
It's not so bad, right?
Still not happy?
I'm still good.
I'm still getting used to this whole "I'm not in love with you" thing.
I'll put down my expectations and send my true feelings Baby Oh
Tiki Bamba Tiki Bamba Tiki Bamba, can you hear me?
Tiki Bamba Tiki Bamba Tiki Bamba Tiki Bamba Tiki Bamba Get this coza...
I'm sure. I'm sure. I'm sure he's feeling it, too.
Countdown in my heart
Hello?
Tissue out.
Tissues out!
It's a tissue. It's not the right size.
Ryu-chan's still out, too.
You're laughing so hard.
Oh, my God!
I'm gonna hold on a second.
It was an accident.
Shoulder.
♪ Heart countdown ♪
Sakira, you're pretty cute.
Wasase, I'm sure you'll love it.
Oh, my God...
You made it! Tish, are you okay?
But I'm really tired...But it really makes me tired many times over.
But it means I could dance.
Success!
Clear!
Then, a little verification
Step verification
Yay!
I'm going to do the Mousaki scary project.
I'd like to do the club step.
Oh, it's not so bad!
This is difficult.
Running
Hey!
Ahhh...
Ha-ha-ha.
It's caught on my skirt.
That's dangerous.
What shall we do next?
Shaburoku.
This is so cool!
Logia label
Logi Label
What? Do I win that?
Yeah.
Ahhh...
Oh, this is difficulty level 5, isn't it?
This is hard.
What is this? This.
I can do this.
Why this one?
How many steps? Let's see...How many steps? Let's see.
Let's see..................
No, there isn't.
It's not a single entry.
It's this one.
What was it?
Oh, that's right.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
What was it?
It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
Maybe that one with the pinwheels will come out next.
A song.
We might play a song by pinwheels.
Let's do at least one more song.
The countdown is that long.
Click, click, click.
The master doesn't seem to like it.
To be honest, I might want him to squat.
It's so bad when he squats.
I thought Iwasaki looked amazing when he was squatting.
It looks like it's tough to get up after squatting.
It's pretty tough.
I wonder if he's going to do it right here too.
Oh no.
Pause click work.
This is not so good.
It's tough.
Let's start the music.
Click to start.
I'm going to push it.I'll drive you to it.
photography 6
pa
ee ee ee.
It's not good.
Oh no!
She's singing.
He's singing.
It's a little off.
Can you do it?
Oh, my God.
This could be bad.
Aahhh! Don't be afraid!
This is really bad!
I missed! I forgot!
So annoying!
I think my leg might have been cramped.
Are you sure you don't want me to get chafed?
Is this a bad place to start?
Really?
I made a mistake.
If I'm going to disappear...
Then expose yourself to me, baby.
I won't let those memories disappear
Get ready for it 3,2,1
Post-it Word
Oh no! Oh no!
Oh no!
Too scary!
Come on!Come on!
Come on!
Oh no! Oh, no!
What? What? What?
This is so boring.
You can't stop!
I was growling on the way over.
I'm sorry, I just have to make an excuse.
I mean, not this one.
Skirt.
I mean...
It's so
Hot.
It's hot.
It's good, isn't it?
You know, it's amazing how people usually dance in heels.
It's amazing.
It's tiring.
Okay, that's enough, right?
I'm fine.
I've got the stamina.
I'll take that as a yes.
Yes, ma'am.
We're...
We were able to dance even with 15cm pinwheels.
You mean you were able to dance?
Yes, it's totally OK.
OK?
Maybe the rating is OK.
I don't know.I don't know.
The people who are watching.
It's not as intense as you'd think.
They don't usually dance around here.
They don't specialize in this kind of thing.
That's why I'm going to test it.
Okay.
Yay!
It was great.
That was great.
I think I'm done.
I'm done.
You're right.
I'm still a model, and my legs are getting fat.
Oh, heels.
You're right, I'd gain muscle.
I'm still a little concerned about it.
Our noses are sweating.
We're all a little...
It's hot.
That's not good.
It's not like we're moving much.
That's right.
We're not moving.
It's dripping down your neck, and you're sweating.
Oh, my God.
You're sweating.
May I?
Is this good?You like this?
It's called cardio.
It's good, right? It's new.
What's that?
It's really good for your core.
It's good for your inner muscles.
That's good.
In a way.
I don't think you have to do this.
And what if I come here to rent a condo? It's annoying.
I'm sure that's what you meant.
Okay, well, thank you very much for watching.
Thank you very much.
I hope you like the video.
If you thought it was a good dance...
Yes, you danced well.
If you think it was well danced, please give it a high rating.
Please subscribe to my channel and leave lots of comments!
Bye bye!